Verle G. Kaiser Papers 1932-1982
Washington State University Libraries: Manuscripts, Archives, and Special Collections (MASC)
- Agronomy, Series 2
  - Principles of Dryland Farming, 1973; 6 items. (Box 3, Folder 217)
  - Principles of Soil Interpretation, 1963; 3 items. (Box 3, Folder 218)
  - "Progress and Problems in Iowa Soil Conservation", 1959; 1 item. (Box 3, Folder 219)
  - Reconnaissance Soil Survey, Nez Perce County, Idaho, 1976; 1 item. (Box 3, Folder 220)
  - Regional Agronomists Meeting, 1950; 1 item. (Box 3, Folder 221)
  - Regional Agronomy Workshop, 1971; 29 items. (Box 3, Folder 222)
  - Regional Soil Conservation Grass School, 1938; 1 item. (Box 3, Folder 223)
  - Report of Agronomy Work in The South Fork Demonstration Project, 1934-1939; 2 items. (Box 3, Folder 224)
  - Salt Tolerance of Plants--Technical Notes, 1965; 1 item. (Box 3, Folder 225)
  - Semi-Annual Agronomy Report, Pomeroy, Wash., 1938; 1 item. (Box 3, Folder 226)
  - Soil and Water Conservation Districts Convention Proceedings, 1971; 1 item. (Box 3, Folder 227)
  - Soil and Water Conservation Needs, A National Inventory, 1965; 1 item. (Box 3, Folder 228)
  - Soil and Water Conservation Newsletter, 1972; 1 item. (Box 3, Folder 229)
  - Soil Classification: Series, Name, Subgroup and Family, undated; 1 item. (Box 3, Folder 230)
  - Soil Conservation Handbook, USDA, 1939; 1 item. (Box 3, Folder 231)
  - Soil Conservation Service, 1962; 1 item. (Box 3, Folder 232)
  - Soil Conservation Service--"The Unfinished Job", 1965; 1 item. (Box 3, Folder 233)
  - Soil Groupings for Nomographs on Terrace Spacing, 1964; 1 item. (Box 3, Folder 234)
  - Soil Management Principles for Conservation of Cropland, Soil Conservation Magazine, 1961; 1 item. (Box 3, Folder 235)
  - Soil Survey Report: White Sands Missile Range, New Mexico; and Hawaiian Conservation Practices, 1971; 5 items. (Box 3, Folder 236)
  - Soils--Classification--General Soil Map, State of Washington, 1967; 2 items. (Box 3, Folder 237)
  - Soils of Washington, Spokane County, undated; 1 item. (Box 3, Folder 238)
  - Soils Section, Whitman County, Washington: Technical Guide, 1956; 1 item. (Box 3, Folder 239)
  - Soils: Special Problems, Correspondence, 1961, l964, 1951; 7 items. (Box 3, Folder 240)
  - Soils: Surveys and Survey Legends, 1939, 1936, 1937, 1939, 1943, 1944, 1947; 11 items. (Box 3, Folder 241)
  - Soils: Surveys and Survey Legends, 1948, 1953, 1954; 6 items. (Box 3, Folder 242)
  - South Palouse Project Reports, 1935-1938; 23 items. (Box 3, Folder 243)
  - South Palouse Project Reports, 1936-1937; 2 items. (Box 3, Folder 244)
  - South Palouse Project Reports, 1937; 1 item. (Box 3, Folder 245)
  - South Palouse Project Reports, 1938; 10 items. (Box 4, Folder 246)
  - South Palouse Project Reports, 1938; 16 items. (Box 4, Folder 247)
  - South Palouse Project Reports, 1939; 16 items. (Box 4, Folder 248)
  - South Palouse Project Reports, 1938-1940; 32 items. (Box 4, Folder 249)
  - South Palouse Project Reports, 1939; 3 items. (Box 4, Folder 250)
  - South Palouse Project Reports, 1939; 2 items. (Box 4, Folder 251)
  - Statement by Verle G. Kaiser, Colfax, Wash., 1953; 1 item. (Box 4, Folder 252)
  - "Straw-Moving System Aids Soil Improvement", 1972; 1 item. (Box 4, Folder 253)
  - Stripcropping on Eastern Oregon Grainlands, 1958; 2 items. (Box 4, Folder 254)
  - Sulphur and Salt Problems, Utah Farmer Journal, undated; 1 item. (Box 4, Folder 255)
  - Sulphur Studies in North Idaho Soils using Radiosulphur, 1959; 1 item. (Box 4, Folder 256)
  - Summary Chart: Generalized Relationship of AASHO Soil Groups and USDA Textural Classes, undated; 1 item. (Box 4, Folder 257)
  - Summary Chart: Generalized Relationship of CE Soil Groups and USDA Textural Classes, undated; 1 item. (Box 4, Folder 258)
  - Summary of the Western Region Agronomy Workshop, Southern California, 1968; 1 item. (Box 4, Folder 259)
  - Summaries of Water-Law Doctrines of the Seventeen Western States, undated; 1 item. (Box 4, Folder 260)
  - Symbols for Western Washington Showing Limitations of Soils in Capability Units, undated; 1 item. (Box 4, Folder 261)
  - Technical Material: Memorandum between Wayne Austin and Verle G. Kaiser, 1958; 18 items. (Box 4, Folder 262)
  - Technical Notes, Soil Conservation Service, 1970; 1 item. (Box 4, Folder 263)
  - Technical Paper: "Clear Your Ponds", undated; 1 item. (Box 4, Folder 264)
  - Technical Publications: Northwest Science, 1967; 1 item. (Box 4, Folder 265)
  - Technical Standards, Specifications, and Notes, 1964; 5 items. (Box 4, Folder 266)
  - The Historical Use of Land and Erosion in the Palouse, Verle G. Kaiser, Northwest Science, 1961; 1 item. (Box 4, Folder 267)
  - The History of Soil Conservation and the Resulting Soil Conservation Act of 1936-1937, 1 item. (Box 4, Folder 268)
  - "The Pyramid of Life," Organisms and Soil, 1960; 1 item. (Box 4, Folder 269)
  - The Release of Fixed Ammonias from Soils, 1963; 1 item. (Box 4, Folder 270)
  - The Royal Bank of Canada Monthly Newsletter, "On Using the Soil Wisely", 1957; 2 items. (Box 4, Folder 271)
  - The Use of Grass in Soil Conservation, undated; 1 item. (Box 4, Folder 272)
  - Tillage of Sweetclover Under Dryland Conditions, 1962; 1 item. (Box 4, Folder 273)
  - Tree Planting for Snowdrift Control and Retirement of Hilltops, undated; 1 item. (Box 4, Folder 274)
  - U. S. Department of Agriculture
    - Soil Conservation Service, 1978; 5 items. (Box 4, Folder 275)
    - Regional Technical Service Center, Portland, 1985; 1 item. (Box 4, Folder 276)
    - SCS Commission, Idaho, 1939-1964; 1 item. (Box 4, Folder 277)
    - SCS, United States, 1952-1977; 11 items. (Box 4, Folder 278)
    - Soil Building Rotation for Weed Control and Conservation, undated; 1 item. (Box 4, Folder 279)
    - Soil Survey: Spokane County, 1968; 31 items. (Box 4, Folder 280)
    - Soil Survey: Spokane County, 1968; 38 items. (Box 4, Folder 281)
    - Soils and Crop Adaptation, Pocket Handbook, undated; 66 items. (Box 4, Folder 282)
    - Soils and Crop Adaptation, Pocket Handbook, undated; 75 items. (Box 4, Folder 283)
  - Washington Lentil Growing Extension Bulletin, Pullman, 1968; 1 item. (Box 4, Folder 284)
  - "We Turn Our Eyes To The Future," Soil Stewardship Week, 1963; 1 item. (Box 4, Folder 285)
  - Western Region Agronomy Workshop, 1971; 2 items. (Box 4, Folder 286)
  - Western Tour and Conference, Spokane, 1941; 1 item. (Box 4, Folder 287)
  - "What Soils Are," Yearbook of Agriculture, 1957; 1 item. (Box 4, Folder 288)
  - Wheat Impact Program of MANR Development and Resources Corporation: Chart, undated; 1 item. (Box 4, Folder 289)
  - Whitman County Soil Survey Legend and Handbook, undated; 4 items. (Box 4, Folder 290)
- Clippings, Series 3
  - "A King's Choice," This Week Magazine, 1965; 2 items. (Box 4, Folder 291)
  - About Friends, 1963-1976; 12 items. (Box 4, Folder 292)
  - Agriculture Miscellaneous, 1964-1979; 6 items. (Box 4, Folder 293)
  - "Another Grain Price Idea Told," Grange News, 1978; 1 item. (Box 4, Folder 294)
  - "Area Farmers Expect Action", undated; 1 item. (Box 4, Folder 295)
  - Article About Verle G. Kaiser The Agronomist; and "Correct Tillage Use," Western Rancher, 1965; 1 item. (Box 4, Folder 296)
  - "Bergland Fears Disaster: Health News, Spokesman Review, 1978; 1 item. (Box 4, Folder 297)
  - Big Game Hunting, 1953-1973; 20 items. (Box 4, Folder 298)
  - Bowling
    - Idaho State Elks Tournament, undated; 8 items. (Box 4, Folder 299)
    - Season Records, 1939-1953; 9 items. (Box 4, Folder 300)
    - Tournament Records, 1948-1981; 17 items. (Box 4, Folder 301)
  - Campus Activities and Disorder at Kent State University and WSU, 1962-1972; 34 items. (Box 4, Folder 302)
  - "Carter to Attack Wheat Surplus", 1977; 2 items. (Box 4, Folder 303)
  - Columbia Plateau Resources Council, 1966-1967; 63 items. (Box 4, Folder 304)
  - Columbia Plateau Resources Council, 1966-1975; 22 items. (Box 4, Folder 305)
  - "Conferees Okay Farm Bill: Veto by Carter Predicted", 1978; 1 item. (Box 4, Folder 306)
  - Crime, 1964-1981; 20 items. (Box 4, Folder 307)
  - Crime, 1980; 7 items. (Box 4, Folder 308)
  - Drought, Inland Empire, 1977; 69 items. (Box 4, Folder 309)
  - Drugs and Marijuana, 1981; 5 items. (Box 4, Folder 310)
  - Education, Mike Royko of the Chicago Sun-Times, undated; 1 item. (Box 4, Folder 311)
  - "Enlarged Farm Bill Expected by Foley, undated; 1 item. (Box 4, Folder 312)
  - Environmental Problems, undated; 26 items. (Box 4, Folder 313)
  - Erosion, San Joaquin Valley, California and Mississippi River Valley, 1981; 1 item. (Box 4, Folder 314)
  - Erosion, 1978-1980; 18 items. (Box 4, Folder 315)
  - Fairfield Standard, 1911; 1 item. (Box 4, Folder 316)
  - Farm Journal, 1981-1982; 14 items. (Box 4, Folder 317)
  - Farm Journal, 1982; 6 items. (Box 4, Folder 318)
  - "Farmers May Seed More Acres Than Ever Before in 1980", 1 item. (Box 4, Folder 319)
  - "Farmers Seek Big Grants to Step Up Erosion Fight," Colfax Gazette, 1979; 1 item. (Box 4, Folder 320)
  - Farming, Erosion, and Soil Conservation, undated; 40 items. (Box 4, Folder 321)
  - Farming, Erosion, and Soil Conservation, undated; 29 items. (Box 4, Folder 322)
  - Field and Stream, undated; 8 items. (Box 4, Folder 323)
  - "Fifty Years of the Soviet Union," Newsweek, 1967; 3 items. (Box 4, Folder 324)
  - Fish and Fishing, undated; 8 items. (Box 4, Folder 325)
  - Fly Tying, undated; 37 items. (Box 4, Folder 326)
  - Foreign Clippings, 1939-1973; 29 items. (Box 4, Folder 327)
  - General Clippings, Spokesman Review, 1977-1978; 5 items. (Box 4, Folder 328)
  - Golf and Softball, undated; 23 items. (Box 4, Folder 329)
  - Governmental Philosophy, 1979-1980; 39 items. (Box 4, Folder 330)
  - Governmental Philosophy: Social Policies, 1980; 1 item. (Box 4, Folder 331)
  - Gun Control, 1968-1981; 44 items. (Box 4, Folder 332)
    - Scopes, undated; 4 items. (Box 4, Folder 333)
  - Health, Social Security and Welfare, 1966-1975; 5 items. (Box 4, Folder 334)
  - "Help For The Farmers," Spokesman Review, 1977; 1 item. (Box 4, Folder 335)
  - "Help For The Farmers," Spokesman Review, 1977; 1 item. (Box 5, Folder 336)
  - Historical Articles
    - Tri Cities, 1956-1981; 23 items. (Box 5, Folder 337)
    - Colfax, 1972-1981; 24 items. (Box 5, Folder 338)
    - Items: Palouse, 1957-1979; 41 items. (Box 5, Folder 339)
    - Miscellaneous, 1978-1980; 10 items. (Box 5, Folder 340)
    - North Central Washington, 1956-1978; 15 items. (Box 5, Folder 341)
    - People and Towns in the Palouse, 1964-1981; 4 items. (Box 5, Folder 342)
    - Scenery of Resources, 1981-1982; 8 items. (Box 5, Folder 343)
    - Spokane and Vicinity, 1957-1964; 21 items. (Box 5, Folder 344)
    - Spokane and Vicinity, 1964-1981; 41 items. (Box 5, Folder 345)
    - Steptoe Butte, 1973-1978; 8 items. (Box 5, Folder 346)
  - How To Do Jobs, 1953-1959; 4 items. (Box 5, Folder 347)
  - Hunting, Fishing, Wildlife, 1962-1981; 15 items. (Box 5, Folder 348)
  - Idaho County Free Press, 1966; 1 item. (Box 5, Folder 349)
  - "Incentive To Reduce Acreage," Spokesman Review, 1978; 1 item. (Box 5, Folder 350)
  - "Increased Erosion Feared," Spokesman Review, 1978; 1 item. (Box 5, Folder 351)
  - Indian and Indian Days in the Inland Empire, 1934-1978; 39 items. (Box 5, Folder 352)
  - Iran News Clippings, 1978-1980; 42 items. (Box 5, Folder 353)
  - Iran News Clippings, undated; 1 item. (Box 5, Folder 354)
  - Kayhan International, 1976; 1 item. (Box 5, Folder 355)
  - "Keep Program Voluntary," The Grange News, 1978; 1 item. (Box 5, Folder 356)
  - Lewiston Morning Tribune, 1960; 6 items. (Box 5, Folder 357)
  - Miscellaneous, 1954-1977; 46 items. (Box 5, Folder 358)
  - Miscellaneous, 1976; 42 items. (Box 5, Folder 359)
  - Miscellaneous, 1978; 15 items. (Box 5, Folder 360)
  - Miscellaneous, 1979-1982; 20 items. (Box 5, Folder 361)
  - Miscellaneous, 1940-1982; 6 items. (Box 5, Folder 362)
  - Miscellaneous, 1979-1982; 11 items. (Box 5, Folder 363)
  - Miscellaneous, 1981-1982; 80 items. (Box 5, Folder 364)
  - Miscellaneous, 1977-1979; 2 items. (Box 5, Folder 365)
  - Miscellaneous, Scrapbook, 1946-1947; 79 items. (Box 5, Folder 366)
  - Mount St. Helens, 1979-1981; 16 items. (Box 5, Folder 367)
  - Mount St. Helens, 1981; 1 item. (Box 5, Folder 368)
  - News:
    - About Verle Kaiser, 1946-1977; 24 items. (Box 5, Folder 369)
    - Forest and Logging, 1946-1968; 9 items. (Box 5, Folder 370)
    - Inland Empire Agriculture, 1954-1968; 32 items. (Box 5, Folder 371)
    - On Conservation: Seed Trade News, 1979; 1 item. (Box 5, Folder 372)
    - Soil and Water Conservation Leaders, undated; 11 items. (Box 5, Folder 373)
  - Newspaper Releases Scrapbook, 1945-1947; 67 items. (Box 5, Folder 374)
  - On Law Enforcement, 1982; 2 items. (Box 5, Folder 375)
  - "Our Great Polluter: U.S. Agriculture," Washington Star Comment, 1978; 1 item. (Box 5, Folder 376)
  - Outdoors Stories of Inland Region, 1954-1965; 23 items. (Box 5, Folder 377)
  - "Palouse Basin: Erosion Real Problem, but Control Possible," Associated Press, undated; 1 item. (Box 5, Folder 378)
  - Philosophy, 1954-1980; 56 items. (Box 5, Folder 379)
  - Pictures, 1934-1974; 40 items. (Box 5, Folder 380)
  - Pictures: Bowling, 1940-1981; 41 items. (Box 5, Folder 381)
  - Pullman Anniversary, WSU Hilltopics, 1981; 1 item. (Box 5, Folder 382)
  - Reports from Washington: National Rifle Association Institute for Legislative Action, 1981; 1 item. (Box 5, Folder 383)
  - Rivers and Dams in the Inland Empire Region, 1954-1977; 24 items. (Box 5, Folder 384)
  - Rockford Farmer Combats Erosion with Diversion Terrace Plan, 1967; 1 item. (Box 5, Folder 385)
  - Science, 1956-1969; 16 items. (Box 5, Folder 386)
  - School Clippings, 1965-1978; 8 items. (Box 5, Folder 387)
  - Season's Records and Analysis, Spokane, 1937-1969; 48 items. (Box 5, Folder 388)
  - "Senate Votes Hike in Subsidies,"Spokesman Review, 1978; 1 item. (Box 5, Folder 389)
  - "Soil Agency is Blamed for Erosion," Spokesman Review, 1977; 1 item. (Box 5, Folder 390)
  - Spokane Daily Chronicle, 1960, 1969; 2 items. (Box 5, Folder 391)
  - Spokane Falls Review, 1886, 1889; 2 items. (Box 5, Folder 392)
  - Sports:
    - Baseball and Softball, 1945-1971; 28 items. (Box 5, Folder 393)
    - Bowling, 1970-1978; 10 items. (Box 5, Folder 394)
    - Miscellaneous, 1936-1979; 38 items. (Box 5, Folder 395)
    - Miscellaneous, undated; 55 items. (Box 5, Folder 396)
  - "Summer Fallow Plans " and "Land Erosion Program is Expected to Pass,"Spokesman Review, 1977; 2 items. (Box 5, Folder 397)
  - "Summer Fallow the Culprit - Kaiser",The Grange News, 1978; 1 item. (Box 5, Folder 398)
  - The "Oregon Hunters' Bag", undated; 1 item. (Box 6, Folder 399)
  - The Kennedys, 1967-1979; 20 items. (Box 6, Folder 400)
  - The Oregonian, 1967; 5 items. (Box 6, Folder 401)
  - The Spokesman Review, 1964-1966; 2 items. (Box 6, Folder 402)
    - "State Population Growth Alarm Bell Sounded", 1978; 1 item. (Box 6, Folder 403)
    - "State Population Growth Alarm Bell Sounded", 1982; 1 item. (Box 6, Folder 404)
  - The Wenatchee Daily World, Columbia River Water Congress, 1966; 13 items. (Box 6, Folder 405)
  - "Topsoil May Soon Replace Petroleum as the Nation's Top Resource," Seattle Post-Intelligencer, 1981; 1 item. (Box 6, Folder 406)
  - USA
    - Newsweek Magazine, 1981, 1982; 6 items. (Box 6, Folder 407)
    - Outside the Northwest, undated; 40 items. (Box 6, Folder 408)
    - Policies, Domestic, 1961-1980; 60 items. (Box 6, Folder 409)
    - Vietnam, 1969-1975; 36 items. (Box 6, Folder 410)
    - Watergate, 1973-1976; 10 items. (Box 6, Folder 411)
    - Presidents, 1963-1964; 11 items. (Box 6, Folder 412)
    - Presidents, undated; 2 items. (Box 6, Folder 413)
    - Relations and Views of Communist Nations, 1950-1972; 14 items. (Box 6, Folder 414)
  - "Variety Galore Rules The Time," Spokesman Review, 1962; 1 item. (Box 6, Folder 415)
  - Vietnam, 1975; 2 items. (Box 6, Folder 416)
  - Water and Resources Problems, 1964-1981; 20 items. (Box 6, Folder 417)
  - "Wheat Production Limits Considered," Spokesman Review, 1977; 1 item. (Box 6, Folder 418)
  - "Wheat Production Limits Considered," Spokesman Review, 1977; 1 item. (Box 6, Folder 419)
  - "Wheatmen Praise Carter Plan," Grange News, 1977; 1 item. (Box 6, Folder 420)
  - "Working Toward A Cleaner Washington," Grange News, 1978; 1 item. (Box 6, Folder 421)
  - Whitman County: Sportsmans' Door Study, 1952; 5 items. (Box 6, Folder 422)
  - Women's Liberation, undated; 5 items. (Box 6, Folder 423)
  - World Resources, 1953-1977; 21 items. (Box 6, Folder 424)
- Correspondence, Series 4
  - Anderson, L.L.E. to Verle G. Kaiser, 1945-1980; 50 items. (Box 6, Folder 425)
  - Appel, Fred: Special Counsel for Committee on Agriculture, 1979; 1 item. (Box 6, Folder 426)
  - Barrett, James: Agricultural Specialist, EPA, 1979; 2 items. (Box 6, Folder 427)
  - Bauer, Lyle: National Association of Conservation Districts, 1978; 4 items. (Box 6, Folder 428)
  - Bauer, Lyle: National Association of Conservation Districts, undated; 1 item. (Box 6, Folder 429)
  - Bauer, Lyle: National Association of Conservation Districts, 1978; 1 item. (Box 6, Folder 430)
  - Berg, Norman: Associate Administrator, SCS, 1979; 1 item. (Box 6, Folder 431)
  - Bergland, Bob: USDA, 1 item. (Box 6, Folder 432)
  - 1978, 1 item. (Box 6, Folder 433)
  - 1978-1979, 3 items. (Box 6, Folder 434)
  - Bertramson, B.R.: Director of Resident Instruction, WSU, 1978; 1 item. (Box 6, Folder 435)
  - Bishop, John, 1963-1972; 5 items. (Box 6, Folder 436)
  - Canode, Chet: Agronomy Department, WSU, 1979; 2 items. (Box 6, Folder 437)
  - Canode, Chet: Agronomy Department, WSU, 1979; 1 item. (Box 6, Folder 438)
  - Cosby, S.W.: SCS, 1950; 1 item. (Box 6, Folder 439)
  - Craig, Alan, 1975-1976; 12 items. (Box 6, Folder 440)
  - Doneen, David J., undated; 3 items. (Box 6, Folder 441)
  - Dubois, Donald P.: Regional Administrator, EPA, 1979; 1 item. (Box 6, Folder 442)
  - Foley, Thomas: Chairman, House Agriculture Committee, 1977-1978; 5 items. (Box 6, Folder 443)
  - Haderlie, Byron, 1980; 4 items. (Box 6, Folder 444)
  - Harker, Michael: Research Associate, University of Idaho, 1977-1978; 3 items. (Box 6, Folder 445)
  - Heinemann, Donald W.: State Executive Director, EPA, 1979; 1 item. (Box 6, Folder 446)
  - Helms, Douglas: Historian, SCS, 1981; 1 item. (Box 6, Folder 447)
  - Hollister, Pat, 1979; 1 item. (Box 6, Folder 448)
  - Hollister, Pat, 1979; 1 item. (Box 6, Folder 449)
  - Hollister, Pat, 1978-1979; 3 items. (Box 6, Folder 450)
  - Hollister, Pat, 1978; 1 item. (Box 6, Folder 451)
  - Jackson, Henry M., 1978; 2 items. (Box 6, Folder 452)
  - Jackson, Henry M., 1978; 8 items. (Box 6, Folder 453)
  - Kline, Frank J.: Project Director, Division of the Environment, Idaho, 1978; 4 items. (Box 6, Folder 454)
  - Krauter, Orlo W., 1966-1972; 3 items. (Box 6, Folder 455)
  - Lawton, Dick, undated; 1 item. (Box 6, Folder 456)
  - Mac, undated; 1 item. (Box 6, Folder 457)
  - Moos, Gene: Executive Officer, House Committee on Agriculture, 1978; 1 item. (Box 6, Folder 458)
  - Moos, Gene: Executive Officer, House Committee on Agriculture, 1978-1979; 3 items. (Box 6, Folder 459)
  - Nanson, Don: Chairman, Conservation Commission, Olympia, 1978-1979; 2 items. (Box 6, Folder 460)
  - Pryse, Doris L., 1965; 1 item. (Box 6, Folder 461)
  - Risser, James: Washington Bureau Chief, Des Moines Register, 1979; 2 items. (Box 6, Folder 462)
  - Risser, James: Washington Bureau Chief, Des Moines Register, 1979; 1 item. (Box 6, Folder 463)
  - Risser, James: Washington Bureau Chief, Des Moines Register, 1979; 4 items. (Box 6, Folder 464)
  - Risser, James: Washington Bureau Chief, Des Moines Register, 1979; 1 item. (Box 6, Folder 465)
  - Risser, James: Washington Bureau Chief, Des Moines Register, 1979; 1 item. (Box 6, Folder 466)
  - Roe, Dennis, 1979; 1 item. (Box 6, Folder 467)
  - Smith, Stewart: Associate Administrator, Agricultural Stabilization and Conservation Service, 1978; 1 item. (Box 6, Folder 468)
  - Tittemore, Rodney, 1979; 1 item. (Box 6, Folder 469)
  - Townshend, Keith, 1979; 1 item. (Box 6, Folder 470)
  - Turelle, Joseph W., 1978; 1 item. (Box 6, Folder 471)
  - Underwood, John: EPA, Seattle, 1979; 1 item. (Box 6, Folder 472)
  - Underwood, John: EPA, Seattle, 1979; 1 item. (Box 6, Folder 473)
  - Wilson, Tom: SCS, 1957; 1 item. (Box 6, Folder 474)
  - Columbia Plateau Resources Council, 1966; 54 items. (Box 6, Folder 475)
  - Columbia Plateau Resources Council, 1966; 63 items. (Box 6, Folder 476)
  - Columbia Plateau Resources Council, 1967; 33 items. (Box 6, Folder 477)
  - Columbia Plateau Resources Council, 1967, 1970; 17 items. (Box 6, Folder 478)
  - Columbia Plateau Resources Council, 1967, 1970; 36 items. (Box 6, Folder 479)
  - Commendations and Criticisms of Verle G. Kaiser, 1938-1967; 70 items. (Box 6, Folder 480)
  - Commendations and Criticisms of Verle G. Kaiser, 1967, 1979; 72 items. (Box 6, Folder 481)
  - Comments on Verle G. Kaiser's Letter to Bob Bergland, 1978; 1 item. (Box 6, Folder 482)
  - Communication Between Verle G. Kaiser and Officers of Colville AC and W Base, 1952; 10 items. (Box 6, Folder 483)
  - Confidential, 1966-1967; 6 items. (Box 6, Folder 484)
  - Correspondence and Records, 1966-1967; 52 items. (Box 6, Folder 485)
  - Correspondence between USDA and Farm Planners of Washington, 1944; 14 items. (Box 6, Folder 486)
  - Correspondence for Rio Suarez Project, Bogota, Columbia, 1966-1967; 32 items. (Box 6, Folder 487)
  - David J. Doneen, Member Public Advisory Committee on Soil and Water Conservation, 1966; 1 item. (Box 6, Folder 488)
  - Dez Irrigation Project, Iran, 1961-1964; 14 items. (Box 6, Folder 489)
    - Resumes and Personal Communications, 1958, 1961, 1963; 41 items. (Box 6, Folder 490)
    - Resumes and Personal Communications, 1961-1962; 13 items. (Box 6, Folder 491)
    - Resumes and Personal Communications, 1963-1965; 52 items. (Box 6, Folder 492)
    - Resumes and Personal Communications, 1960-1963; 69 items. (Box 6, Folder 493)
  - General Correspondence, 1965, 1975-1979; 16 items. (Box 6, Folder 494)
  - General Correspondence, 1977-1979; 36 items. (Box 6, Folder 495)
  - General Correspondence, Palouse Wheat Allotment Program, 1977; 5 items. (Box 6, Folder 496)
  - General Correspondence, Palouse Wheat Allotment Program, 1978; 19 items. (Box 6, Folder 497)
  - Guns and Ammunition, 1953-1956; 8 items. (Box 6, Folder 498)
  - Joseph W. Turelle, SCC, Portland to R.L. Kent, Spokane, 1965; 1 item. (Box 6, Folder 499)
  - Letter by David J. Doneen to Dr. Louis L. Madson, W.S.U., 1966; 2 items. (Box 6, Folder 500)
  - Letters from J.W. Cronwall:
    - Letters, 1961, 1966; 12 items. (Box 6, Folder 501)
    - on Agriculture and Conservation, 1957-1981; 78 items. (Box 6, Folder 502)
    - on Guns and Gun Control, 1961-1975; 14 items. (Box 6, Folder 503)
    - on Hunting, Fishing and Recreation, 1946-1978; 14 items. (Box 6, Folder 504)
    - on Miscellaneous Subjects, 1943-1978; 25 items. (Box 6, Folder 505)
    - on History of the Pacific Northwest, 1958-1979; 33 items. (Box 6, Folder 506)
    - to and from Members of Congress, 1951-1978; 20 items. (Box 6, Folder 507)
  - Memorandum:
    - Luke J. Best, 1958; 1 item. (Box 6, Folder 508)
    - Barry, Austin and Homer, 1961; 1 item. (Box 6, Folder 509)
    - Joseph Turelle, 1966; 1 item. (Box 6, Folder 510)
  - Miscellaneous, 1962-1968; 9 items. (Box 6, Folder 511)
  - Miscellaneous, 1968-1970; 13 items. (Box 6, Folder 512)
  - Miscellaneous, 1976; 8 items. (Box 6, Folder 513)
  - Miscellaneous, 1978-1979; 7 items. (Box 6, Folder 514)
  - Mixed Correspondence, 1947-1955; 7 items. (Box 7, Folder 515)
  - Narrative Trip Reports and Technical Correspondence, 1965-1966; 36 items. (Box 7, Folder 516)
  - Narrative Trip Reports and Technical Correspondence, 1955-1965; 57 items. (Box 7, Folder 517)